Jason Heyne

Communications Technician

Los Angeles, CA jasonheyne314@gmail.com 458.226.5603

Traveling and living in the varied environments that I have, a unique skill set has been crafted out of different training techniques, cultures, and problems that appeared. I am thrilled to troubleshoot equipment, and thrive out in the field.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Soldering Technician

Ascentron - White City, OR July 2017 to December 2017

Became certified to solder components to PCB boards, worked as part of an assembly crew.

IT Technician

IKonectu - Nashville, TN March 2016 to June 2017

A one person outfit, this was me doing the installations for a friend who owned an IT consulting firm in Nashville, Tn.

I installed gear in rural areas to boost cell signal strength, deployed wifi networks in high-rise buildings, and built/terminated network racks.

Service Implementation Technician

Impulse Advanced Communications - Santa Barbara, CA April 2012 to May 2014

This is where I was able to see the other side of the installation, and work for a Managed Service Provider. Coming from a legacy PBX environment, this company needed my skills to ID various circuits from whomever, and bring those circuits to the customer premises. I also performed site surveys for the phone installations, leaned how to navigate my way through network gear with a usb cable and some sort of CLI, and trained companies on their new phones.

Communications Technician III

Bassett Medical Center - Cooperstown, NY February 2011 to December 2011

A large Healthcare facility. I received a lot of corporate training here, including how to behave properly and respectfully towards your co-workers. My core role was to support

the Enterprise PBX located at the main Hospital facility, as well as the private branches at the clinics, all over upstate NY.

Telecommunications Technician

Automated Answering Systems - New York, NY April 1999 to April 2004

June 2008 - January 2010

Where I started as a Technician. I worked my way up from being hired as a cable runner to learning and programming the Partner ACS system, after that it wasn't long before I was out on my own, performing site surveys for CAT3/5 installs all over New York City. Became accustomed to remote programming and high pressure environments.

Education

High school or equivalent in Art

Bayside High School - Bayside, NY September 1991 to June 1994

High school diploma

Skills

- Assembly
- Soldering
- T1
- Cisco
- Cabling
- Networking
- CCTV
- Time Management
- Network Installation
- Telecommunication
- VolP
- LAN
- Network Support

Certifications and Licenses

driver's license